





Summary

Jump to Section

Certified Project Management-PRINCE2 Foundation with over 15 years of experience with over 7.5 years in Business Analysis, Strategic Consulting, Thought Leadership, Product/Project Management and Stakeholder & Team Management and nearly 7+ years in Core Development with key focus on profitability and optimal resource utilization

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Work Experience

APT IT Solutions as Consultant Business Analyst Aug 2018 to Till Date

Responsible for functional/non-functional requirement gathering, solution mapping, requirement analysis and preparation of business requirement documents along with the creation of the help file for the system. Serving as a liaison between technical and non-technical departments. Communicating with other management, developers, product managers and technical support specialists on product issues. Maintaining process documentation

- ? Preparing Functional Specification Documents deriving from Business Requirements. Ensuring technical solutions are designed for performance, reliability, scalability, maintainability and supportability while leveraging industry?s best practices.
- Object Technology Solutions as Business Analyst Mar 2015 to Jun 2018

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.A (Political Science) from Nagarjuna University in 1998

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Prince2 project Management Paticipated certified workshop for CPBA

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
AXURE	9	2020	6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

MS Visio	7	0	6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Balsamiq		0	6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: software engineer

Client: AMEX

Nature of Employment: Full Time Project Location: pune Role: Programmer

Skill Used: uml using msvisio,mockup-axure,usecase
Role Description: implementing and designing ,modeling and prepaing as a BRD,FRD,mockups
Project Details: as a java developer creating web pages uaing spring,hibernet and database then moved to associate

business analyst

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

Duration: Mar 2010 - Jul 2014

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 10

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.